<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Beeline</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1840650169531250</string>

    <!-- Login activity -->
    <string name="app_title">beeline</string>
    <string name="tag_line">Direct path to highest mutual attraction.</string>
    <string name="login_button_label">Log in with Facebook</string>
    <string name="background_content_description">Background texture</string>
    <string name="facebook_login_canceled">Facebook login was cancelled.</string>
    <string name="facebook_login_failed_toast">Something unexpected went wrong with the Facebook login.</string>
    <string name="facebook_login_no_connection_toast">Facebook login failed due to a lack of connection. Restore the connection and try again.</string>

    <!-- Introduction deck activity -->
    <string name="getting_started_button">Get started</string>
    <string name="rate_users_title">Pick the one you like better</string>
    <string name="rate_users_body">
        Help the algorithm determine your unique dating preferences.
    </string>
    <string name="rate_users_graphic_content_description">
        Illustration that depicts two profiles shown side by side and suggests the user to pick the
        preferred one.
    </string>
    <string name="get_matched_title">Get matched for maximum mutual attraction</string>
    <string name="get_matched_body">
        Tired of hundreds of matches that go nowhere? Based on your ranking, we know exactly who
        is into you.
    </string>
    <string name="get_matched_content_description">
        Illustration that depicts dating matches.
    </string>
    <string name="start_a_conversation_title">Start a small number of high quality conversations</string>
    <string name="start_a_conversation_body">
        Through mutual ranking, you will have much higher quality prospects. Everyone is
        limited to contact only the 10 best matches daily. Start a genuine conversation now!
    </string>
    <string name="start_a_conversation_content_description">
        A diagram that shows message bubbles.
    </string>

    <!-- CropPhotoActivity -->
    <string name="crop_photo_activity_title">Crop</string>
    <string name="delete_button_label">Delete</string>
    <string name="cancel_button_label">Cancel</string>
    <string name="select_profile_photo_chooser">Select profile photo</string>
    <string name="crop_failure_toast">Something went wrong cropping the image.</string>

    <!-- ViewOwnProfileActivity -->
    <string name="age_separator">,\u0020</string>
    <string name="profile_info">Profile Info</string>
    <string name="deactivate_account_link">Deactivate account</string>

    <!-- EditProfileActivity -->
    <string name="edit_profile_activity_title">Edit profile text</string>
    <string name="profile_edit_text_hint">Enter a short profile</string>
    <string name="discard_button_content_description">Discard button</string>
    <string name="characterCounter">%1$d / %2$d</string>
    <string name="profile_builder_upsell">Try the profile builder</string>
    <string name="profile_builder_upsell_action">Build</string>

    <!-- RatingActivity -->
    <string name="distance_snippet">&#160;(%1$d miles)</string>
    <string name="choose_hint">or</string>
    <string name="first_selection_dialog_header">You tapped a profile</string>
    <string name="first_selection_dialog_message">
        Tap a profile to tell us that you prefer that person.
        \n
        \nWe\'ll show you the next profiles to compare.
    </string>

    <!-- No more pairings available activity -->
    <string name="no_more_pairings_heading">
        There are no more pairings available.
    </string>
    <string name="no_more_pairings_message">
        Beeline has only recently launched. Your support is
        critical for starting profiles.\n\nUnfortunately, there are no more users in your area to
        vote on. Please, stick with us.\n\nWe\'ll notify you if someone new signs up in your area.
    </string>

    <!-- Matches Activity -->
    <string name="matches_activity_title">Your matches</string>
    <string name="no_matches_heading">You do not have any matches</string>
    <string name="no_matches_message">
        Rank more profiles to find people who like you back.\n\n
        Beeline is a brand new app. There may not be any profiles left to rank. Be a hero and
        stick with us.
    </string>
    <string name="match_lock_icon_title">Match lock explanation</string>
    <string name="match_lock_icon_explanation">
        Once you message a match, that match becomes locked. The daily algorithm won\'t remove the
        match.\n
        \n
        If you like the person, message them quickly. Not that into it? No worries. Keep ranking
        more profiles.
    </string>

    <!-- Messages Activity -->
    <string name="no_messages_message">Break the silence! Send a message!</string>
    <string name="enter_message_hint">Type your message</string>
    <string name="send_button_content_description">A button that sends the current message.</string>
    <string name="fuck_off_button_content_description">This is the famous fuck off button.</string>
    <string name="fuck_off_dialog_title">The famous fuck off button</string>
    <string name="fuck_off_dialog_text">
        Warning! This action cannot be undone! You will NEVER hear from this person again. \n
        \n
        Please, think long and hard before proceeding. Based on your preferences, we\'ve given you
        the best match that\'s interested in you. If you reject this person, you\'ll get
        the next person on your list. If you ranked them right, you are going to
        like them less.\n
        \n
        But, if you\'re absolutely sure this isn\'t going anywhere, then do the merciful thing. Throw this person back into the wild
        and tell \'em to fuck off!
    </string>
    <string name="fuck_off_menu_title">Fuck off</string>
    <string name="today_date">Today</string>

    <!-- View profile activity -->
    <string name="view_profile_title">User Info</string>
    <string name="fuck_off_label">Fuck off</string>
    <string name="report_label">Report</string>
    <string name="report_button_content_description">A button to report a user</string>

    <!-- About Activity -->
    <string name="about_app_heading">About Beeline App</string>
    <string name="about_app_body_text">
        Compare-to-rank revolutionizes online dating. Dating is a two sided problem. You can find
        out the hard way who likes you through weeding outs tons of “hi” messages that go nowhere.
        Or you can use Beeline.
        \n
        \nWe\'ll show you two profiles, and you pick the one you feel more attracted to. The app will
        ask you to compare your favorite profile against another winning profile. Choosing the same
        profiles over others again? They’re definitely your soulmates. (Just kidding. But they are
        your top picks.)
        \n
        \nAt the same time, everyone else compares and ranks profiles. Once a day, an algorithm
        matches people for the highest mutual attraction. Think mutual super likes, not simple
        swipe-right likes.
    </string>
    <string name="about_background_heading">In-Depth</string>
    <string name="about_background_body_text">
        Tired of endless unanswered messages? Totally over those awkward “hello\'s” that go nowhere
        and ready to match with someone who really likes you back?
        \n
        \nWith Beeline, you are in control of who matches with you. Why trust an algorithm to pick
        your soulmate anyway? A computer can match two people with similar interests, but it can\'t
        determine the why behind why they do what they do. Just because they both love Daredevil
        doesn\'t necessarily mean they’re compatible.
        \n
        \nWe, on the other hand, constantly size up people and choose who we want to get to know. We
        spend our lives reading people. With Beeline, you get to keep reading people. You are the
        algorithm.
        \n
        \nSound too good to be true?
        \n
        \nA game-proof mechanism ensures that if your guy chose you, he truly picked you over
        everyone else.
        \n
        \nHere\'s how: You\'ll be shown two profiles side by side. We\'ve distilled robust
        information on each person into an easy-to-read profile. You decide whom you you\'d rather
        date: Artsy boy with a soft spot for vegan ice cream, or sexy geek who enjoys jazz shows?
        Over consecutive comparisons, you teach the app which guys you find most attractive.
        Repeatedly picking the same guy over others? He might just be your other pea in a pod.
        \n
        \nAnd get this: Guys go through the same process. They also have to choose one girl over the
        others, so there can be only a handful of girls who keep winning. (Think no swiping right on
        every girl.) Only those with the strongest mutual attraction get matched.
        \n
        \nAt this point, you have both handpicked each other. It’s not just a swiped, casual like.
        You can send each other meaningful messages assured that there is high mutual interest.
        \n
        \nSay goodbye to low-investment matches. Say hello to meaningful conversations and highest
        mutual attraction.
    </string>
    <string name="about_faq_heading">FAQ</string>
    <string name="about_faq_body_text">
        <b>Q: I find rating people demeaning.</b>\n
        A: We do, too! Beeline is not about rating people. You choose whom you’d rather meet based
        on the profiles you see. Do you prefer a snowboarder over a hobby gardener?\n
    \n
        <b>Q: What if I like both profiles?</b>\n
        A: The same profiles will come up in future match-ups. Taking all these match-ups together,
        the app will realize that you like them both very similarly.\n
    \n
        <b>Q: What if I select the wrong profile by mistake?</b>\n
        A: Don\'t worry about it. The app will match-up the profiles against other profiles later.
        The wrong tap will be recognized as an anomaly. Simply keep comparing more profiles.\n
    \n
        <b>Q: This seems like a popularity contest.</b>\n
        A: Beeline only matches you with people who really like you back, which means you are free
        to be yourself. Enjoy a relaxing night in writing poetry and listening to Coltrane? Love
        being the life of the party? You may just find a special someone who is into that, too.\n
    \n
        Another unique aspect of the app is “local peaks” in the distribution: Within certain
        subgroups different people win the popularity contest. Say if you are a skateboarding punk,
        you are likely attracted to people inside of that group. If you love hiking and nature, you
        are likely attracted to people inside of that group. Beeline helps you find your people.\n
    \n
        <b>Q: Why am I not getting matched with the people that I select?</b>\n
        A: With Beeline, we cut to the chase: you only get matched with people who really like you
        back.\n
    \n
        <b>Q: I don’t have anybody to compare!</b>\n
        A: Beeline is a brand new app with an innovative and superior approach, but enough users
        have to give us a chance to get this off the ground. If you don’t have anyone to match, it
        means you are the first person in your area. Help us out: tell your single friends about
        Beeline!\n
    \n
        <b>Q: How can I close my account?</b>\n
        A: This is a brand new app, and we are still adding more features. Go to your profile and
        look in the lower right hand corner for a link to deactivate your account.
    </string>
    <string name="about_feedback_heading">Send Us Feedback!</string>
    <string name="about_feedback_body_text">
        I\'d love to hear from you. Send your feedback to
        <a href="mailto:thomas@playposse.com?subject=Feedback About Beeline Android App">thomas@playposse.com</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="about_credits_heading">Credits and copyright</string>
    <string name="about_credits_body_text">
        © 2017 Thomas Fischer\n\n
        The logo is a combination of artwork from the <a href="thenounproject.com">thenounproject.com</a>:\n
        Lion by Polina Flegontovna from the Noun Project\n
        Middle Finger by Piotrek Chuchla from the Noun Project\n
        Sad emoji by Weltenraser from the Noun Project\n
    </string>


    <!-- No connectivity activity -->
    <string name="no_connectivity_heading">The network is unavailable.</string>
    <string name="no_connectivity_message">
        To prevent errors, Beeline will continue when network access is restored.
    </string>


    <!-- Profile not ready activity -->
    <string name="profile_not_ready_heading">Not so fast!</string>
    <string name="profile_not_ready_message">
        Before you get to look at profiles, you have to complete your own profile.
        \n
        \nPlease ensure that you have a main photo and bio.
    </string>


    <!-- Deactivate account activity -->
    <string name="deactivate_account_warning">You are about to close your account.\n\nI personally read all comments. This is my baby, I try to make it better. Your feedback might help me direct my efforts to where they are most needed.</string>
    <string name="deactivate_account_reason">Reason</string>
    <string name="deactivate_account_button">Close account</string>
    <string name="deactivate_account_cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="deactivate_account_confirmation">Your account is closed.\n\nFacebook may still show this app for you. To remove it from Facebook, you have to do so on Facebook.\n\nIf you want to come back, simply start this app and sign in again.</string>


    <!-- Reactivate account activity -->
    <string name="reactivate_account_title">Re-activate Account</string>
    <string name="reactivate_account_welcome">I\'m glad to you are giving Beeline another try.\n\nLet me know if I can do anything to make your experience better this time. You can use the send feedback link in the navigation drawer to contact me. I personally read those messages.</string>
    <string name="reactivate_account_button">Reactivate</string>


    <!-- Age request activity -->
    <string name="age_request_title">How old are you?</string>
    <string name="age_request_message">Inquiring minds want to know.\n\nTogether with gender and distance, it\'s a key decision factor for romantic partners.</string>
    <string name="age_request_legend">month/day/year</string>
    <string name="age_request_button">Save and continue</string>
    <string name="age_request_required_error">Cannot parse. Please, format as \'month/day/year.\'</string>
    <string name="age_request_future_error">So, you say you are from the future! I don\'t think so.</string>
    <string name="age_request_super_old_error">Old is sexy. But go ahead tell us your true age.</string>


    <!-- No location activity -->
    <string name="no_location_title">Where are you?</string>
    <string name="no_location_message">We can\'t match you if we don\'t know where you are.</string>
    <string name="grant_location_permission_button">Grant permission</string>
    <string name="check_location_button">Check my location</string>

    <!-- Admin statistics activity -->
    <string name="total_user_count">Total user count</string>
    <string name="active_user_count">Active user count</string>
    <string name="rating_count">Ratings count</string>
    <string name="match_count">Matches count</string>
    <string name="conversation_count">Conversations count</string>
    <string name="admin_statistics_report_duration">Report generation duration (ms)</string>

    <!-- Profile Builder -->
    <string name="profile_builder_title">Profile builder</string>
    <string name="reset_link">Reset</string>
    <string name="back_button_button">Back</string>
    <string name="next_button_button">Next</string>
    <string name="done_button_button">Done</string>
    <string name="profile_builder_page_index">%1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="profile_builder_intro_heading">Welcome to Profile Builder</string>
    <string name="profile_builder_intro_message">
        Having a short, concise profile with the most important information up front is critical.\n
        \n
        Users absorb profiles quickly to create a gut reaction and vote.\n
        \n
        This profile builder will help you create a profile snapshot like this:\n
        \n
        <b>Santa Monica, CA - Wants long-term / engineer / no kids / yogi, adventurer / must like
        dogs</b>\n
        \n
       Remember: Choose your words carefully. Potential matches wil see only a short Twitter-size message.
       Feel free to add more text for your actual matches. While it won\'t show up in comparison, it\'ll be visible once you\'re matched.
    </string>
    <string name="profile_builder_intro_footnote">* all steps are optional</string>
    <string name="profile_builder_optional_hint">(Optional)</string>
    <string name="profile_builder_other_hint">e.g. adventurous barefoot doctor</string>
    <string name="profile_text_reorder_instruction">Rearrange the items in desired order.</string>
    <string name="profile_options_separator">,\u0020</string>
    <string name="profile_questions_separator">\u0020|\u0020</string>
    <string name="other_option_label">Other:\u0020</string>
    <string name="confirm_save_profile_title">Confirm</string>
    <string name="confirm_save_profile_body">Replace profile?</string>
    <string name="confirm_reset_title">Confirm</string>
    <string name="confirm_reset_body">Reset profile builder?</string>


    <!-- Navigation drawer -->
    <string name="drawer_open">Navigation drawer opens</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Navigation drawer closes</string>
    <string name="profile_nav">Profile</string>
    <string name="rating_nav">Comparing</string>
    <string name="matches_nav">Matches</string>
    <string name="send_feedback_nav">Send feedback</string>
    <string name="about_nav">About</string>
    <string name="logout_nav">Log out</string>


    <!-- Activity selection bar -->
    <string name="profile_activity_selector">Profile</string>
    <string name="rating_activity_selector">Comparing</string>
    <string name="matches_activity_selector">Matches</string>


    <!-- Progress loading dialog -->
    <string name="progress_dialog_title">Crunching data…</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_message">Please be impatient and drum your fingers!</string>

    <!-- Location permission dialog -->
    <string name="location_permission_dialog_title">Bzz! Where are you?</string>
    <string name="location_permission_dialog_message">
        To find your perfect match, we gotta know where you are. Please, enable the location
        service.
    </string>

    <!-- Discard dialog -->
    <string name="discard_dialog_title">Discard changes?</string>
    <string name="discard_dialog_message"> </string>
    <string name="discard_dialog_cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="discard_dialog_discard_button">Discard</string>

    <!-- Photo picker dialog -->
    <string name="photo_picker_dialog_title">Photo</string>
    <string name="photo_picker_dialog_pick_item">Pick</string>
    <string name="photo_picker_dialog_delete_item">Delete</string>
    <array name="photo_picker_dialog_items">
        <item>@string/photo_picker_dialog_pick_item</item>
        <item>@string/photo_picker_dialog_delete_item</item>
    </array>

    <!-- Report abuse dialog -->
    <string name="report_abuse_dialog_title">Report Abuse</string>
    <string name="report_abuse_dialog_note_hint">Describe the abuse issue.</string>
    <string name="report_abuse_dialog_button">Report</string>

    <!-- Session expired dialog on the login activity -->
    <string name="session_expired_dialog_title">Session expired</string>
    <string name="session_expired_dialog_message">
        Your session has expired. Please, log in again.\n\n
        Note: Your session will automatically expire when you sign into a different device.
    </string>
    <string name="login_connectivity_dialog_title">No network!</string>
    <string name="login_connectivity_dialog_message">This app requires network access to log in with Facebook and to connect you with awesome people!</string>
    <string name="firebase_id_missing_dialog_title">Waiting for Firebase id</string>
    <string name="firebase_id_missing_dialog_message">Please, ensure that you have internet connectivity and the Google play services installed.</string>

    <!-- Send Us Feedback option -->
    <string name="feedback_dialog_title">Send us feedback!</string>
    <string name="feedback_dialog_message">An e-mail will open where you can send me feedback.</string>
    <string name="feedback_email_recipient">thomas@playposse.com</string>
    <string name="feedback_email_subject">Feedback About Beeline Android App</string>
    <string name="feedback_email_body">Please, send me your feedback. I care about hearing from you.</string>

    <!-- Common text -->
    <string name="save_button_label">Save</string>
    <string name="dismiss_button_label">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="profile_photo_content_description">The profile photo of a user.</string>
    <string name="profile_thumbnail_content_description">The thumbnail of a profile photo of a user.</string>
    <string name="lock_icon_content_description">A lock icon that indicates if a profile is locked or not.</string>
    <string name="new_message_icon_content_description">An icon that indicates that a new message has arrived.</string>
    <string name="love_icon_content_description">A heart shaped icon that indicates that you like that user.</string>
    <string name="info_icon_content_description">Info icon</string>

    <!-- Feature discovery -->
    <string name="app_info_title">How The Algorithm Works</string>
    <string name="app_info_body">
        1. Choose between two profiles repeatedly.
\n2. Find your repeat top choices.
\n3. Sit tight while others make their picks.
\n4. Discover your top 10 mutual attraction matches.
    </string>

    <string name="comparison_info_title">Compare profiles</string>
    <string name="comparison_info_body">
        1. Review the profiles.
\n2. Tap your preferred profile for a date.
\n3. Rinse and repeat.
    </string>

    <!-- Common button labels -->
    <string name="dialog_okay_button">Okay</string>
    <string name="dialog_continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="dialog_cancel_button">Cancel</string>

    <!-- Notifications -->
    <string name="updated_matches_notification_title">
        Woohoo! Beeline has new matches for you!
    </string>
    <string name="updated_matches_notification_text">
        The algorithm just finished running. You\'ve been matched!
    </string>

    <string name="only_lost_matches_notification_title">
        You\'ve had some matches in Beeline. Now they are gone.
    </string>
    <string name="only_lost_matches_notification_text">
        Don\'t worry! Rank more profiles to find who likes you back.
    </string>

    <string name="new_message_notification_title">
        New message!
    </string>
    <string name="new_message_notification_text">
        Check out what a cutie\'s writing you!
    </string>
    <string name="unmatch_notification_title">Unmatched</string>
    <string name="unmatch_notification_text">You have been unmatched.</string>
    <string name="not_logged_in_notification_title">Matches were recalculated!</string>
    <string name="not_logged_in_notification_text">Please, log in to check if there is someone new for you!</string>


    <!-- Survey snackbar -->
    <string name="survey_snack_bar_prompt">Help me improve the app!</string>
    <string name="survey_snack_bar_action">Take survey</string>


    <!-- Admin menu -->
    <string name="admin_menu_statistics">Statistics</string>
    <string name="admin_menu_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="admin_browse_users">Browse users</string>

    <!-- Admin toasts -->
    <string name="admin_refresh_success_toast">Successfully refreshed the admin database.</string>
</resources>
